ninefold.com 2012-12-29

# Privacy Policy | Legal | Ninefold cloud computing Australia - Ninefold

#### Our commitment to privacy

Ninefold® Pty Ltd (Ninefold) respects your rights to privacy under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). We are required to comply with the National Privacy Principles in respect of the collection, use, disclosure and handling of personal information from individuals.

This Privacy Policy governs the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Ninefold. By visiting our website, or otherwise providing your personal information to Ninefold via other means, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

#### What type of information do we collect?

Personal information is any information that can be used to identify you. The types of personal information that we collect from our customers includes: name, telephone, email and credit card details.

#### How do we obtain personal information?

Ninefold collects personal information via the following methods:

  * when you participate in our blog;
  * when you send us emails. These email messages will contain your screen name and email address, as well as any additional information you may wish to include in the message;
  * via the website's server, relating to your navigation of this website. The types of information collected can include browser type, IP address, the URL you have come from and your domain type and server;
  * from "cookies" used in some sections of the website. A "cookie" enables this website to customise its services to each individual user. It also tracks navigation in the site and stores that information on your hard drive. You should be able to "opt out" of receiving cookies by setting your browser to recognise when a cookie is offered and opting-out of receiving it. You should check with your software manufacturer or Internet Service Provider to determine how you can alter your browser's settings. Any "cookies" used at this website are used only to facilitate use of this website. Ninefold does not use "cookies" to collect and distribute information for any other purpose;
  * at the 'Contact Us' section of the website, which enables you to use the online form to submit an enquiry and any specific question to Ninefold. In order to process your enquiry, we request that you complete the online form by providing certain personal information, such as contact details. If you send an email, we require the same information;
  * at the online services part of the website. To use these services we require you to type in your user identification and password. Before you gain access to these services, we collect some personal information; such as the names of individuals, their contact number, credit card details and position, who are authorised by their organisation to use the access user identification and password and the online facilities associated with these services. Our server tracks the user identification and passwords that are used. In turn, this usage provides information about an individual's use of the online services.

#### What do we do with the information?

Once collected, the personal information is stored in our databases. Some information relating to billing or other contract management is handled through our Software as a Service (SAAS) partners and may be stored and processed offshore. However, if you choose to purchase cloud virtual servers and storage services from us, all of your cloud data is hosted in Australian data centres.

Your personal information may be used to:

  * handle orders
  * verify your identity;
  * assist you in the provision of our services;
  * administer and manage those services, including charging, billing and collecting debts;
  * conduct appropriate checks for credit-worthiness; and
  * deliver targeted and non-targeted marketing information to you about our services. When we first contact you for the purpose of direct marketing however, we will give you the opportunity to opt out of receiving any further marketing communications from us. You can also contact us as outlined below, to request that we do not send you any further information;

If we wish to use any of your personal information for purposes other than those listed above, we will only do so with your prior consent.

#### Do we disclose your personal information to others?

Ninefold understands that any personally identifiable information that it collects from you is strictly confidential. We do not share, sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information except in the following circumstances if applicable:

  * contractors / providers: In order to provide the services to our customers, we may exchange information with contractors, suppliers, carriers or carriage service providers;
  * to conduct credit checks; and
  * where we are required by/or allowed by law, regulation or industry codes, for safety reasons or where we reasonably believe that you are in breach of the terms of use of our website or are engaging in unlawful activities.

#### How do we protect your personal information?

We take all reasonable steps to maintain the security of your personal information that we collect. We use a variety of secure techniques to protect your information from unauthorised access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure. For information that is stored on electronic databases, we use secure servers, firewalls, and restrict access by only allowing those personnel that 'need to know' the information, access to that information using passwords. Credit card information is stored on a PCI compliant billing system. For information that is not stored electronically, Ninefold ensures that our employees and contractors understand that personal information is only to be reproduced strictly where necessary and always stored and treated confidentially.

Online or electronic data transmission (whether information you transmit to Ninefold or that we transmit to you using your personal information) is not 100% secure. Therefore, any online activity by you in connection with the website is conducted at your own risk, despite our best endeavours to ensure the security of the information that is transmitted between us.

#### Accessing your personal information

You may access any personal information that we hold about you at any time after validating your identity. We will handle requests for access to personal information in accordance with the Privacy Act. To request access to your personal information, please contact us by any of the means set out below.

You may request that we change any of your personal information in order to update the information or remove your personal information that you have provided to us. Once we receive your written request, to the extent possible, we will provide you with a copy of that part of your personal information you requested or an accurate summary of your personal information. We will also invite you to request any correction or deletion of the personal information and we will confirm with you once we have corrected or deleted the personal information. We reserve the right to retain information if required to do so by any applicable laws.

If for any reason, you consider that we have not responded to your requests adequately, please contact us.

#### Contact our Privacy Officer

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, request for access to or correction of information held by us or any complaint regarding the treatment of your privacy by us, please email us at privacy@ninefold.com or write to us at:

Attention: The Privacy Officer (Legal Department)  
Ninefold Pty Limited  
Level 20, 2 Market Street  
Sydney NSW 2000

We may change this privacy policy from time to time and will notify you by posting an updated version of this policy on our website at ninefold.com.

This document was first published on 26 January 2011.

© 2012 Ninefold Pty Limited
